<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Auckland Museum</title>
    <link>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Auckland Museum</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Auckland Museum - Human Interface Digital Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>The aim of the Auckland Museum Human Interface Guidelines (HIGs) is to promote a coherent digital visitor experience throughout galleries and exhibitions - maintaining the look and feel over time and across interfaces.
The HIGs are for developers and designers who are creating digital experiences for Auckland Museum.
The HIGs are based on our Digital Experience Design Principles, augmented by Google&amp;rsquo;s Material Design, and Te Papa&amp;rsquo;s Digital Language System.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auckland Museum Assets</title>
      <link>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/auckland-museum-assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/auckland-museum-assets/</guid>
      <description>Brand Depending on your project, you may or not be required to use the Auckland Museum logo and frame branding device. However, it&amp;rsquo;s worth being aware of our brand guidelines.
 Auckland Museum Brand Design Guidelines, September 2017  Style Guide Currently available as a project resource, this document presents the Museum&amp;rsquo;s written conventions for print and on-screen. Contact your project manager for a copy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing for the Museum context</title>
      <link>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/designing-for-the-museum-context/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/designing-for-the-museum-context/</guid>
      <description>Our Visitors The visitor journey often starts outside of the physical Museum via the Auckland Museum website or social media channels outside, which lead to a museum visit, and multiple passive and active digital interactions during the stay. Visitors may collect or generate personalised content to take away or build-upon after their visit, and these interacts with our online channels may lead on to their next visit.
The wide audience range of Auckland Museum creates interesting challenges for interactive designers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Experience Design Principles</title>
      <link>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/digital-experience-design-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/digital-experience-design-principles/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Auckland Museum DXDPs were developed over a number of iterations and include insights from an environment scan across international museums. They have been peer reviewed by the Museum&amp;rsquo;s Digital Advisory Group.
Extending the Gallery Renewal Principles and Visitor Market research insights, the Digital Experience Design Principles are high-level statements around &amp;lsquo;digital experiences&amp;rsquo; at Auckland Museum.
 Digital as an enabler Digital technology is only used when it serves a specific need and not merely for technology&amp;rsquo;s sake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inclusive Design</title>
      <link>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/inclusive-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/inclusive-design/</guid>
      <description>Digital products must be universally accessible. Some elements of accessibility will sit outside of your brief, such as placement and casing for an interactive.
Adhere to the accessibility guidelines from Te Papa and Material Design.
You do not have to use the exact dp sizes specified by Material Design, but ensure you have adequate touch target spacing and icon sizes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UI Text</title>
      <link>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/ui-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/ui-text/</guid>
      <description>Multilingual Interfaces You may receive more guidance on the use of te reo Māori as part of your brief.
You must also adhere the Auckland Museum style guide, found here. This includes guidelines on the use of te reo Māori.
Please also refer to the Te Papa UI control names.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX and UI Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/ux-and-ui-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/ux-and-ui-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Icons The Museum uses the Material Design icons, and a community created set which includes outline versions of the icons. The table below indicates which icons we use for each function. Most icons will appear in a button or as part of an AV player.
 Download our selected Material Icons here.  File names in this package are referred to below.
Icon Usage In general, use outline versions of icons, contained in a button, where available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Design Foundations</title>
      <link>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/visual-design-foundations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aucklandmuseum.github.io/human-interface-guidelines/visual-design-foundations/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The foundational elements of print-based design – typography, grids, space, scale, color, and use of imagery – guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus.&amp;rdquo;  Material Design
 Typography Gotham Narrow is the Auckland Museum typeface. We use two variations of Gotham Narrow — Regular and Bold. This typeface must be used in all digital products. The Gotham Narrow Font family was designed and is distributed by Hoefler &amp;amp; Co.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>